淘宝搜索店铺：我爱美剧创意周边
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译:  斑驳      正面赛太公反面周渝民
翻译:  洗七里    Eunice油腻希
校对:  正面赛太公反面周渝民
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第二十集
最新海外影视剧下载
微信扫描
上方二维码
关注TV哔
一起哔哔哔
杰和我合伙开了个停车场
Jay and I are partners in a parking lot,
这为我们的感情增添了新活力
and it's added a wonderful, new dynamic to our relationship.
第一步是要雇人在收费亭收费
The first step was hiring someone to man the booth.
我们将候选范围缩小到了来应征的两个人
We narrowed it down to the two candidates who applied.
我认为与其让人们觉得
I don't think it should be,
"我真希望我总去吃午餐的餐厅
"I hope there's a place to park
旁边有个方便停车的地方"
near where I love to have lunch."
不如让人们觉得
I think it should be,
"我真希望我总去停车的停车场
"I hope there's a place to have lunch
旁边有个方便吃午餐的地方"
near where I love to park."
那么  蒂伯
So, Tibor,
跟我们说说在停车场工作让你激动的理由
tell us why you're excited about a career in parking.
工作好
Is good.
这个问题很难回答
That's a tough one.
在我心里排名前三的是
My top three...
真命天女组合
Destiny's Child...
-珍妮·杰克逊  -太棒了
- Janet Jackson... - ‭Yes.
和我的最爱  金属乐队
and my fave... Metallica.
我的天  你的口味真多元化
Oh, my goodness, you are so complex.
蒂伯  你最喜欢哪个流派的音乐
Tibor, what are your favorite kinds of music?
蒂伯
Tibor.
不错吧
Is good?
我认为该选谁显而易见
Well, I think the choice is clear.
-蒂伯  -琼
- Tibor. - Joan.
蒂伯
Tibor?
我喜欢他的热情  因为他没有热情
I like his energy. He doesn't have any.
我喜欢琼  她很有趣
Well, I like Joan. She's fun.
那就请她看电影去  这是做生意
Take her to the movies. This is a business.
看来我们意见又不统一了
Looks like we're at a stand-off.
天啊  别掏硬币
God, not the coin.
哪怕像我和杰这样的超级好伙伴
Even super-duper pals like Jay and I
也有意见相左的时候
disagree sometimes,
于是  我想到了这个宝贝主意
so... I dreamed up this baby.
如果是菲尔这面朝上  我赢
If it comes up Phil, I win.
如果是杰这面朝上  他赢
If it comes up Jay, he wins.
他特别讨厌这枚硬币  但我告诉他
He hated this, but I told him,
"谁的脸铸到硬币上看起来都胖九斤"
"The coin adds 10 pounds."
这次游行会特别激进吗
So, how hard-core is this march going to be?
只是一群和平的女人
Just a peaceful gathering of women
共同为性别平等这个目标而努力
working towards the same goal of equality.
不会集体烧文胸什么的
We're not burning bras or anything.
那就好  因为我刚买了第一件文胸
Good, 'cause I just got my first one.
要烧也得等我穿着它去内奥米家过夜之后
I'm not torching it before Naomi's sleepover.
今天肯定会让你觉得特别激动人心  莉莉
This is a really exciting time for you, Lily.
这是你第一次体验到女权
This is your first taste of feminism.
我们在座的都是你的良师益友
We're all here as your mentors --
或者说"娘师益友"
or "Womentors".
给点反应  我刚发明的新词
Come on, I just coined that.
你说"如英雌一般"时我们假笑过了
We fake-laughed at "Sheroic."
实在没心情配合你了
The well is dry.
这车堵得太荒唐了
This stupid traffic!
看看这么多的女司机  莉莉
Look at all these women in these cars, Lily.
多激励人心啊
It's so inspiring.
人人为我
All for one!
-我为人人  -我走小路绕过这些白痴
- One for all -- - I am gonna cut around these idiots!
那是什么声音
What was that?
有人开枪把车胎射爆了
Somebody shot out the tire!
不是吧  你第一个想到的就是这个吗
Really? That's where you go with this?
分明是路面上的坑
It was a pothole.
仪表盘开始乱闪了
The dashboard is going crazy.
车胎瘪了  "太好了"
It's a flat tire. Perfect.
我这种有胸的人不知道"瘪"是什么意思
I wouldn't know about "flat."
菲尔  菲尔
Phil! Phil!
咱有麻烦了
We have a problem.
"咱"吗
"We"?
我想去那家卖熊爪包的面包房
I'm trying to get to that bakery that makes those bear claws.
你和你的破硬币雇的那个话唠
That chatterbox you and your coin hired
害我们停车场排起了长队
is clogging up our parking lot.
太好了  又损失八美元
Oh, great. There goes eight bucks.
这是正式的合伙人会议吗
Is this an official partners' meeting?
等一下
Hold on.
早上好  欢迎
Good morning and welcome.
目前在场的合伙人有
Partners present --
菲尔·邓菲  把你那个白痴本子放下
Phil Dunphy -- Put down your stupid notebook.
是你想雇她的
You're the one who wanted to hire her.
你得告诉她要么提高效率要么走人
You've got to tell her to speed it up or hit the road.
我想让您知道您的问题我都清楚了
I want you to know that I hear you
我会尽快处理
and will address this posthaste.
现在  不如我们谈一谈上次会议中
Now, if we could move on to some unfinished business
没有谈完的问题
from the last meeting, um...
"我的感情仍然很受伤
"My feelings are still hurt
因为听你对我说了
from you telling me
你想让我把硬币塞到哪些糟糕的地方去"
all the places you want me to put the coin."
都十点多了
Ah, it's after ten o'clock --
这个时候吃熊爪包太晚了
too late to eat a bear claw now.
吃那么多糖我会兴奋得睡不着午觉的
I'll be too sugared up for my nap.
一切都毁了
Everything's ruined!
看来你在忙
Hey. You look busy.
我不过是最后点缀一下
Oh, yeah, well, I'm just putting the finishing touches
今年校园音乐剧要穿的戏服
on the costumes for this year's school musical.
是那部你声称根据你的人生故事改编
You mean the one that's supposedly based on your life,
但一词一曲都照抄《绿野仙踪》的音乐剧吗
but is a beat-for-beat rip-off of "The Wizard of Oz"?
我的故事讲的是一个早熟的农场小子
Mine is the story of a precocious farm kid
踏上一段魔幻旅程去大城市冒险
who takes a magical journey to the big city.
哪里抄《绿野仙踪》了
How is that "Wizard of Oz"?
小卡  你的故事里也有个铁皮人
Cam, you have a Tin Man.
绿野仙踪是讲一个小女孩去魔幻国度
与稻草人  狮子  铁皮人一同冒险的故事
那是我们高中的吉祥物
That's our high-school mascot.
我们的吉祥物是神力奶壶
We were the Mighty Milk Jugs.
你知道的
You know this.
帕姆
Hi, Pam.
二位
Hey, y'all.
听着  楼上的厨房里...
Listen, upstairs in the kitchen...
有没有...
is there, um...
那个什么...
one of those, uh...
就是那个什么...
you know, things that, uh...
等等  你刚刚问我什么来着
Wait, what were you asking me?
帕姆  你还好吗
Pam, are-are you okay?
妹子  你看起来累坏了
Oh, honey, you look exhausted.
宝宝昨晚又闹了一整晚
The baby didn't sleep again last night.
跟你说  自从咱家被龙卷风卷飞以来
I'll tell you, I haven't been this out of sorts
我还是第一次累成这幅德行
since that twister lifted up our house.
这回信我了吧
Told ya.
那次龙卷风特别厉害
That wind was so strong
把我们所有的玉米粒都剥光了
it shucked all our corn.
就像...  每次...
‭It was like... whenev--
-她睡着了吗  -别担心  她没事
- She sleeping? - No, she's fine.
我们家犁地的马以前也总这样
Our plough horse used to do the same thing.
宝宝哭了
Baby's crying.
不如我停一停手里的活
Why don't I put this on pause.
上楼去帮你一把
I'll come up and help you out for a little bit.
还是让米奇尔来帮忙吧
Oh, maybe Mitchell should help.
他特别会安抚小卡尔霍恩
He's just so good with baby Calhoun.
我该叫你"抱小孩魔手舅舅"
Aww. ‭I ought to call you "Uncle Secret Touch".
这昵称听起来有点像
That seems like a
"法律规定不准接近儿童公园"的那种人
"500 feet away from a playground" kind of nickname.
不过我很愿意帮忙
But I will be happy to help.
那好  我就在这待着以防没人找我帮忙
Okay, well, I'll just be down here, in case nobody needs me.
不如你先上楼
Hey, wh-why don't you head upstairs.
我马上就上去  好吗
I-I'll be right up, okay?
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
你总是想把自己这一面藏起来
You know, you try to hide it,
但你这人特别多愁善感
but you are a sensitive soul...
"偷偷有感觉[摸]舅舅"
"Uncle Sneaky Feeler."
我们把这昵称传出去前再商量商...
Yeah, before we go wide with that, let's, um --
别  好吧
not. Okay.
小卡
Cam.
怎么  我觉得他叫你去帮忙照顾小卡尔
What? I think it's great that she's asking you
而不找我这个血亲
to help out with baby Cal
是件很好的事
instead of his own flesh and blood.
看来她只有在让我戴假发
I guess the only thing I'm good for
替考她的SAT时才会想到我
is putting on a wig and taking her SATs.
我真不敢相信你居然会嫉妒
I cannot believe you're jealous.
我才没嫉妒  我忙得很
I'm hardly jealous. I'm much too busy.
忙着做完飞猴的戏服吗
Oh, finishing the flying monkeys?
在绿野仙踪里有出现
它们不是飞猴
They're not flying monkeys.
我问问你  你觉得负鼠被龙卷风卷起来后
Let me ask you -- what do you think happens
会变成什么样
to possums during a tornado?
停到那边那辆别克旁边
Park it over there, next to that Buick.
看看谁来了
There he is.
琼  今天这儿怎么样啊
Hey, Joan. How's everything down here today?
我让车辆入位  人们面露微笑
Putting cars in spaces and smiles on faces.
除了还没让你微笑
Well, except for yours.
怎么了
What's wrong?
没事  很好  没错  真的很好
Oh, no, I'm good. Yeah, definitely good.
菲尔  我最懂的两件事
Phil...if there's two things I know,
就是人和停车
it's people and parking.
你看起来像遭遇了困境
And you look like you trying to get out of a tough spot.
被你一眼看穿了
You see right through me.
我们的合伙人会议上有个问题
There was an issue at our partners' meeting.
等一下
Hold on one second.
亲爱的
Hey, sugar!
亲  工作派对怎么样
All right, girl, how was the office party?
这次我一直穿着衣服呢
I kept all my clothes on this time.
你是对的
And you were right --
远离混酒  宿醉全无
I stayed away from mixers and I'm not hungover!
是吧
See?!
没有酒就不会输
You can't lose if it's nothing but booze.
这值得来一发
That deserves...
彩纸屑炸弹
confetti bomb!
你人最好了
You're the greatest.
在那个蓝色丰田旁边停车
Park it over there by that blue Toyota.
好样的
My girl!
她是个小酒鬼
She is a bit of a drinker,
所以我总给她很大空间
so I like to give her a lot of space.
好啦
All right.
你要说什么
Now, what did you want to talk about?
没什么
Nothing.
这一切都很完美
Everything here is perfect.
-接近完美  -你想到什么吗
- Well, almost. ‭- Something on your mind?
没什么  不过一整天
No, but something is on my feet
我的脚上都有东西  我自己
all day -- me.
收费亭加个橡胶垫怎么样
How 'bout...a gel mat for the booth?
我会给你装个垫子
Oh, I'm getting you a mat...
因为你太棒了
'cause you're all that.
我好喜欢
I love that!
彩纸屑炸弹
Confetti bomb! ‭
我不是在检查他的工作
It wasn't like I was checking up on him.
我午休后来吃午后熊爪包  经过这儿
I had my nap and I came by for an afternoon claw.
我现在没啥事干了
I don't have a lot going on right now.
我觉得是这个
I think it's this one.
亲们  咱们打电话给道路救援吧
Hey, guys, why don't we just call roadside assistance?
我想他们会派个人过来的
I'm sure they'll send somebody.
如果今天是为了女人力量而出来
If today is all about girl power,
我们为什么不自己修好
why can't we just fix it ourselves?
我就知道我们不该带她
I knew we shouldn't have brought her.
真有意思
It's funny --
我们在女性示威游行做志愿者
we've only been volunteering here
-只有一个小时  -五分钟
- at the women's march for an hour... - Five minutes.
但我已经感觉我是
...but it already feels like I'm part of something big,
这个盛大又特别的活动的一部分
something really special.
你能给我拍张照片吗
Would you snap a picture?
这样你就能证明你有来  然后拿到学分
So you can prove you were here and get school credit,
在你的海报上拼错的字母干了之前
and be home faster than the ink dries
你就可以回家了
on that poster you just misspelled?
女性解衣[联合]
"Women Untie"?
拼错也通啊
Still works.
卢克  这些女性值得我们的尊重
Luke, these women deserve our respect.
她们要克服
They've had to overcome
我们无需面对的偏见和挑战
biases and challenges we've never had to face.
她们是女性选举权运动人士的后代
They're the granddaughters of the suffrage movement.
坐等你的小演讲结束
Sitting through your little speech...
也是种折磨[选举权]
that's suffrage.
天啊
Oh, my God.
那是微积分课上的丹妮尔·帕尔多
I-It's Danielle Pardo from calculus.
-谁  -你不会认识她的
- Who? - ‭You wouldn't know her.
你们在不同的圈子
You run in different circles.
她在荣誉尖子班  而你
She's in honors classes and you, well,
只是在兜圈子
run in circles.
曼尼
Hey, Manny!
很高兴看到你在这
It's so cool you're here.
我也在这  卢克·邓菲
And I'm here, too -- Luke Dunphy.
你现在看到我
You saw me now
一直到游行结束时你也会看到我
and you saw me at the end of the march.
如果你们在做牌子
If you guys are making signs,
我有些议题
here are some of the issues --
1块钱的活儿  女性只能赚到79美分
women make 79 cents on the dollar,
还有  女性能不能打胎居然是政府来决定
and the government wants to tell me what I can do with my body.
你如果是你  你什么感受
I mean, how would you feel if --
她让我太震惊了
She blew my mind.
社会把女性当成二等公民对待
Society treats girls like second-class citizens.
我在"女性网站"上花了很多时间
I've spent a lot of time on women's websites,
但从没见过这些信息
but none of this stuff ever came up.
莉莉  你看  强大的女子在行动
You're watching strong women in action, Lily.
当我们一起动脑
When we put our minds together,
没有什么是我们做不到的
there's nothing we can't achieve.
这太难了
This is too hard.
我放弃
Ugh. I give up.
看下说明书吧
Let's just get the manual.
好主意  我喜欢
Great idea. I like that.
莉莉  这不是童话故事
You see, Lily, there are no fairy tales,
没有等待拯救的女子
no damsels in distress.
我们有的可不止
We are more than just a bunch
漂亮脸蛋
of pretty faces.
工作箱里除了化妆品  啥也没有
There's nothing in the glove box but makeup.
不错  因为放了说明书
Ay, yeah, because the manual wouldn't fit
我的紧急补妆箱就放不下了
with my emergency touch-up kit.
我想再次建议
I would like to revisit
歌洛莉亚的提议  放弃
Gloria's idea about giving up.
那可真是积极的榜样
Oh, that's setting a great example.
如果当年居里夫人放弃研究
What do you think would've happened
你觉得会发生什么事
if Marie Curie had given up?
她就不会死于辐射中毒
She wouldn't have died of radiation poisoning.
你怎么会知道这个的
How on Earth did you know that?
你总是提她
You talk about her a lot.
直到我在一张邮票上看到她之前
Until I saw her on that stamp,
我以为她是你女朋友
I thought she was your girlfriend.
歌洛莉亚  我不敢相信你不知道怎么换轮胎
Gloria, I can't believe you don't know how to change a tire.
你之前是出租车司机  你肯定遇过爆胎吧
You drove a taxi. Surely you had a flat.
我遇过很多次爆胎
I had a lot of flats,
但我就再化化妆  然后等一会
but I would reapply my makeup and I would wait and then,
五分钟之内  就会有一队的男人替我换了
in five minutes, I would have my own pit crew.
我们换好这个轮胎后
You know, after we get this tire changed,
你是还想去游行
do you still want to go to the rally
还是我们该把你丢去旧社会
or should we just drop you off in 1950?
亲们  那里...
Uh, guys, there's, uh...
需要帮忙换胎吗
You need help with that tire?
不不  我们不用  我们很好  谢谢
No. ‭No. No, we don't. We're good, thanks.
你们在说什么
What are you guys talking about?
她是个女的  她想帮我们换轮胎
She's a woman and she wants to help with the tire.
所有条件都符合啊
She checks all the boxes.
好吧
Right. Um...
你好
Hello.
我们想换轮胎
Uh, we were trying to change our tire,
但千斤顶出了点问题
but there's something wrong with the jack.
让我看看
Let me check it out.
那个呀
Uh-huh. Oh, that.
好了
Okay. ‭There we go.
应该动那个
...should have moved that one.
你被雇佣了
You're hired.
太好了  来把这车撑起来吧
Great. Let's get this baby off the ground.
我叫乔伊
I'm Joey, by the way.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我是海莉
I'm Haley.
怎么  她超酷  让我有点意乱情迷
What? She's awesome, it's confusing.
我读了你的剧本  亲爱的
I read your script, baby.
如果第三幕有问题
If you got third-act problems,
第一幕也有问题
you got first-act problems.
你说的太对了
You are so right.
挨着那个本田停
Park it next to the Honda
把你的反派再写得更细致点
and flush out your antagonist.
-你好  -你好  杰
- Hey. - ‭Hey, Jay.
歌洛莉亚  曼尼  乔  斯黛拉怎么样啊
How's Gloria, Manny, Joe, and Stella?
怎么  你是有提词小抄吗
What, do you got index cards?
听着  你喋喋不休把这里弄得一团乱
Listen, your chattiness is gumming up the works here.
我们不是请你来社交的
You're not here to socialize,
就让他们进去停车  完事出来就行
so just get 'em in, get 'em out.
你是在叫我别跟大家聊天吗
Are you asking me not to talk to people?
这可是我的招牌
'Cause that is what I do.
再说菲尔对此也没意见啊
And Phil don't seem to have a problem with it.
他没  但我有
No, but I do.
引用小萨米·戴维斯的话
Well, to quote Sammy Davis Jr.,
"我必须忠于自己"
"I got to be me."
美国传奇黑人歌手  演员
那我也引用法兰克·辛纳屈的话
Well, to quote Frank Sinatra,
有次在餐厅遇见他  他对我说
who I met once at a restaurant,
美国白人爵士歌手  流行音乐领军人物
"从我的卡座[收费亭]滚出去"
"Get out of my booth."
行啊
Okay.
老娘
Fine...
没意见
with me.
我停在哪儿
Hey. Where do I park?
停在格子里
Between two lines.
扛南瓜[打壁球]的旧患又痛了
Ugh, my old squash injury.
你以前打壁球吗
Oh, you played squash?
不是啦  我种出了一个全县最重的南瓜
No. I grew the heaviest one in the county.
我每晚都得把它搬进屋里
I had to carry it inside every night,
否则会有小偷来偷
on account of poachers.
卡尔霍恩小宝贝
Hi, little baby Calhoun.
我是你的舅舅小卡
It's your uncle Cam --
我才是你的亲舅舅  而不是米奇尔
your real uncle, not that guy Mitchell,
他不过是我在某派对上遇到的路人甲
who's just somebody I met at a party.
我和你会成为世上最要好的朋...
You and I are gonna be the best friends in the whole wide --
不不不不不
No, no, no, no!
你干嘛要弄醒宝宝啊
Why would you wake the baby?!
-我只是...  -好不容易才把他哄睡着了
- Well, I just was... ‭ - He was finally asleep!
-我只是...  -我来抱他
- I was just... ‭- I-I got him.
让我来  没事的
I got him. It's gonna be okay.
过来  宝宝
Come here, baby.
-好了  -谢谢你
‭- Okay... - Thank you.
我差点要比玛格丽特公主看到男友
I was about to wig out worse than Princess Margaret
被伊丽莎白女王驱逐时更惊慌失措
when her boyfriend was banished by Elizabeth.
就是啊
Oh, yep.
你们看《王冠》没叫上我吗
You watched "The Crown" without me?!
讲述英女王伊丽莎白二世的电视剧
-来  卡尔  -好
- Come on, Cal. - Yeah.
这位暴躁女王的戏码一点都不好看
It's no fun watching this angry queen.
我真是不敢相信
I can't believe you.
我们只看到第四集
We're only on episode four
而且也没剧透你啊
and there are literally no spoilers.
我是指你和你那个怪异的新家庭
I'm talking about you and your weird, new, little family.
你让宝宝讨厌我了
You have turned that baby against me.
你跟他说了我什么坏话
What did you say to him?
小卡  只有你会认为这是负面的事
Cam, only you could turn this into something negative.
我和你姐姐变得亲近并没有什么问题
There's nothing wrong with your sister and I becoming closer.
我们之间的关系很特别
We have a very special relationship --
有点像女王和她的私人秘书那样
kind of like the one the queen had with her private secretary.
你个爱剧透的贱人
You son of a bitch!
史实又谈何剧透啊
It's history.
你知不知道  世界500强企业里
Do you know that there are only a handful
只有一小部分执行总裁是女性
of female C.E.O.S in the entire Fortune 500?
那太不合理了
That's crazy.
女性驾驶赛车的技巧跟男性一样棒
Women can drive a racecar just as well as a man.
卢克误把500强误会为近似的赛车联赛
你真幽默
You joke.
我还在上高中  就已经每天都遇到性别歧视
I'm only in high school and I see casual sexism on the daily.
我知道  我听到伊斯顿老师总是对你"男解"
I know. I hear the way Mr. Easton "mansplains" everything to you.
-那是什么  -是指男性给女性
- What's that? - It's when a man tries to
解释她本已知道的事情
explain something to a woman that she already knows.
你是在男解"男解"给我听吗
Are you mansplaining "mansplaining" to me right now?
我问的是你手上的零食
I was talking about your snack.
这是什锦果仁[先河]
It's trail mix.
你知道还有谁开创了先河吗  杰罗丁·费拉罗
You know who else blazed a trail -- Geraldine Ferraro!
美国第一位主要政党竞选副总统的女性候选人
琼  是我
Hey, Joan, it's me...
蝙垫侠
Mat-man.
你在这儿干什么  琼呢
What are you doing here? Where's Joan?
你本该跟她讲清楚  但你没有
You were supposed to handle it, but you didn't,
所以我百忙之中抽空过来
so I had to take time out of my extremely busy day
想跟她说清楚
and try to straighten her out.
但她不肯按我说的去做  所以只能请她走了
But she didn't go along with the program, so she's gone.
你没跟我商量就把她赶走了
You did this without talking to me?
我们不是一起做决定的搭档吗
We're supposed to be partners.
我们会请那个叫蒂伯的
We're gonna hire that Tibor guy.
他几乎不会说英语  但这样就不会喋喋不休了
He barely speaks English, but there'll be no chattiness --
虽然我也试过对歌洛莉亚用这招
although I did try that with Gloria,
但他们最终还是会通过看大量电视学会讲英语
and eventually they watch so much TV they figure it out.
-可是硬币已经决定了啊  -去你的破硬币
- But the coin decided. - Screw the coin!
没人需要排队  停车场也比琼以前工作时还满
There's no line, and Joan never had this many cars in the lot.
大家都喜欢她  她很擅长这份工作
People liked her! She was good at this!
淡定  只是停车而已  不像造衣柜那么难
Relax. This is parking cars, not building closets.
不好意思
Excuse me?
我的车子被四辆车挡住了  出不来
There's like four cars blocking me in.
我马上帮你移走
I'll get them out of your way in a jiffy.
不要
Oh, no!
糟糕
‭Oh, no!!
确实很"糟糕"  一大波瑜伽课学员正杀来
"Oh, no" is right. The yoga class just got out.
你先站在这个上面
Here, stand on this.
你可能要在这儿等很久
You might be here for a while.
好棒
So good.
小帕
Pam?
好了
Hey -- okay.
我们到床上去睡
L-Let's go to bed.
我不累
No. I'm not tired.
不  你脖子和肩膀老是酸痛
No, this is why your neck and shoulders always hurt,
就是因为你总是不躺着睡
'cause you're falling asleep standing up.
来  我扶你到床上
Come on, let's get you to bed.
来吧
Come on.
好吧  好吧
‭Okay, all right.
我的王子
Ah, my prince.
苍天啊
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
苍天啊
都给我淡定  冷静点  冷静点
All right, everybody relax. Calm down! Calm down.
谁开丰田普锐斯
Who drives the Prius?
钥匙上串着超市积分卡
With a "Whole Foods" reward card?
琼人呢  我得赶紧取车
Where's Joan? I need my car.
彩纸屑炸弹
Confetti bomb.
没停车位了
We're full.
没事了  我把琼请回来了
Everything's fine. I've rehired Joan.
我们不需要她
We don't need her.
谁的车钥匙是银色的
Who drives the car with the silver keys?
菲尔  到底要不要我出马
Phil, am I doing this or not?
琼  停车场就交给你了
Joan, the lot is yours.
好了  温蒂  你快开走那辆小货车
All right. Wendy, let's get you in that minivan
回家照顾你患糖尿病的猫
and home to your diabetic cat.
你不能单方面重新雇用她  菲尔
You cannot unilaterally rehire her, Phil.
就像你不问过我就把她炒掉一样吗
You mean like how you fired her without talking to me?
如果我们有异议
If we disagree about something,
就该通过掷硬币来做决定
we're supposed to flip over it!
也许我们该掷硬币看看  还要不要继续合作
Maybe we should flip over whether we should even be partners.
-也许我们现在就该掷  -很好
- Maybe we should do it right now. - ‭Great.
如果是菲尔那面  我们继续合作
If it comes up Phil, we keep going.
如果是杰那面  我们终止合作
If it comes up Jay, we end it.
你们两个傻子在干什么
What are you two fools doing?
我们合作不来
This isn't working out.
合作愉快的前提是
And it's not gonna
你要平等对待这个人
until you start treating this man like your equal.
你以为自己是了不起的大老板
You think you're some big-shot boss
可以肆意欺负他
and you can just push him around.
-谢谢你  琼  -闭嘴
- Thank you, Joan. - ‭Zip it!
你任由他欺负你
You let him do it.
帮你自己个忙
Do yourself a favor --
向杰学习学习  比如如何强硬点
learn something from Jay, like how to be tough.
你们才不需要这个破硬币
You guys don't need a stupid coin.
你们只需要彼此
You need each other.
现在  说点好听的
Now...say something nice.
我一直  一直很欣赏你的霸气
I always -- I always have admired your toughness.
好了  该你了
All right. Your turn.
我一直觉得你很...
I always thought you were...
快乐
...happy.
看见没
See?
这才是撒彩纸屑的正确方式
And that is how you do that.
你回来了
Oh. Hey, there you are.
是我错了
Listen, it was wrong of me
说你跟小帕之间
to say something weird was going on
有些不寻常的关系
between you and Pameron.
我脑子肯定哪里抽风了
I don't know what I was thinking.
你们俩很明显有着完美正常的
Clearly, you guys have a perfectly normal
姐姐与同性恋弟媳的关系
sister- and gay-brother -in-law relationship.
你在宝宝监视器上看到了是吧
You saw it on the baby monitor, didn't you?
在夜视画面里看更显诡异
It was even creepier in night vision.
我也一脸懵逼啊
I don't know what happened.
你们俩有着一样的香唇  而且...
Y-You both have the same lips and --
一样的吻法...
and you kiss the same and --
我们对同一根篱笆支柱练的吻技
We did learn to kiss on the same hedge post.
米奇尔  能借一步说话吗
Mitchell, could I speak to you in private, please?
怎么  你还想再来几发拥颈亲热吗
Why? Do you want to do some more neckin'?
你还四处炫耀了吗
You were bragging on it?!
他从婴儿监视器上看到的
He saw it on the baby monitor.
你还偷看  你个淫虫蛤蟆
And you were watching, you horny toad?
小帕  冷静
Pam, let's calm down.
你这样是在给自己找难堪
You're kind of embarrassing yourself.
我知道
I know!
我就是一团乱
I'm such a mess!
我好累啊
I'm just so tired!
而且我看着女皇的马交配那一幕到睡着
Plus, I fell asleep to the scene of the queen's horses doin' it!
-喂喂喂  别剧透啊  -没什...
- Hello? Spoiler alert. - It's just...
对不起我给你们增加负担了
I'm sorry if I've been such a burden.
-没有  你才不是负担  -没有  你不是
- No, you're not a burden. ‭- No, no, you're not a burden.
起来  听我说
No, come on, listen --
说实话  其实我挺享受
the truth is, I've kind of enjoyed
当一个宝宝的超厉害爸爸
being super-daddy to a baby,
因为我从没体验过这感觉
you know, 'cause I've never had that.
你说什么呢  你当时也很会照顾莉莉啊
Oh, what are you talking about? You were great with Lily.
不  是你很会照顾莉莉
No, you were great with Lily.
而一开始时  我...
In the beginning, I...
我也是一窍不通  所以我都让你主导
I was a mess, so I let you take the lead.
我也说不上  或许我只是
I don't know, m-maybe I'm just
想证明点什么给自己看吧
trying to prove something to myself.
亲爱的  我不知道你有这想法
Oh, sweetie, I had no idea.
但你真的不需要证明什么
But you don't have anything to prove
因为你已经是很棒的父亲了
because you're a great dad.
你们俩都是
You both are...
但我真是烂透了
but I'm a disaster.
别  白沙发  起来吧
No, white couch. Let's get you up.
我觉得光靠我一个人照顾不来啊
I don't think I can do all this by myself.
那有个好消息就是
Well, you know what, the good news is,
你不需要一个人照顾
is you don't have to do any of this all by yourself,
因为你的楼下有爱你的家人
because you have a family right down here who loves you
会愿意为你做任何事来帮助你
and will do anything we need to do to help you.
太好了  这对我太意义非凡了
Good. That means the world to me.
而且...  我知道这哭声的意思
And besides... I know that cry,
这尿片我不去换
and somebody else is changing that diaper.
-我不去  -我不去
- Not it. - Not it.
所以女人怎么都输啊
So, women can't win.
女人去工作要受不公平对待
They're penalized if they work
而在家当家庭妇女也一样
and they're penalized if they stay home.
没错
Exactly!
卢克  在我今早起床
You know, Luke, when I woke up this morning
来到这场游行前
and came to the rally...
我从没想过我会遇到像你这样的人
I never thought I would meet somebody like you.
轮到你了
You're up!
到我了
It's my turn.
真不敢相信她会信你的烂招
I can't believe she's falling for this.
我这一生都支持女权
I've believed in this cause my whole life.
而你只花一个下午来假装一下
You spend an afternoon faking it
她就亲到你嘴唇边上了
and she kisses you almost on the lips.
我才没有假装什么
I'm not faking anything.
她打动了我
She got through to me.
女人  女孩  以及支持我们的男性
Women and girls and the men who honor us...
我国女人所要遭受的不公简直就是犯罪
It's a crime what women in this country have to go through,
我全心全意支持她
and I'm with her 100%.
不作出牺牲  就永远成不了大事
We will never accomplish anything without sacrifice.
没错
Damn straight!
对不起  我也不是故意要这样
I'm sorry. I didn't mean for it to happen, but...
但我跟丹妮尔真的是心灵相通
Danielle and I made a connection
无论要多久  我都会在她身旁支持她
and I'm sticking with her as long as it takes.
所以在女人得到真正的平等之前
That's why, until women have true equality,
我决定当独身禁欲者
I will remain celibate.
咱们走人吧
Let's get out of here.
现在千斤顶放下来了
Now that the jack is lowered
螺母也都拧上
and all the lug nuts are snug,
就只差交叉把它们都拧紧了
you just got to tighten everything in a cross pattern.
何不你们一人来拧一个呢
Why don't you each do one?
如果可以的话  我不想身上沾到油污
If it's okay, I'd rather not get grease all over me.
要想改变世界
Hey, you can't change the world
必定满手泥泞
without getting your hands dirty.
好吧  给我
Okay. Give me that.
你说得真对
You're right.
这感觉好棒
This is great.
感觉我无所不能
It feels like I can do anything.
你这是在转松
You're loosening it.
不好意思  对不起
Oh. Oh, sorry.
谢谢你  乔伊
Thank you, Joey.
你换胎的速度好快
You did that so fast.
车子是我血液里的一部分
Well, cars are in my blood.
我的奶奶自己开了一家修车厂
You know, my grandmother ran her own garage.
太厉害了
Huh. That's so awesome.
在那种年代一定有各种偏见
There must have been a lot of prejudice back then.
的确  但后来呢
There was... but eventually,
她还是帮忙爱尔兰佬修车了
she started fixing Irish people's cars.
莉莉  你去把剩下的转紧吧
Well, uh, Lily, why don't you finish it off.
我不够力气
I'm not strong enough.
我来帮你
Well, then let me help you.
我们联手力气更大
We're stronger together.
我们联合的确更强大
Wow. We are stronger together.
对不起我之前看轻你
Oh, I'm sorry I put you down before.
你是个很强大的女人  歌洛莉亚
You are a formidable woman, Gloria.
你值得受人尊敬
You deserve respect.
不  克莱尔  你才值得受人敬重
No, Claire, you are the one that deserves respect.
你养大了三个很棒的孩子  经营了一家公司
You have raised three wonderful children, you run a company,
不浪费时间在鸡毛蒜皮的小事
you don't waste time on silly things like...
比如搞发型之类的
the way your hair looks.
你会把该做的事都做好
You just get things done.
这样就好了  你们能重新上路了
And that is it. You guys are all set.
真的很谢谢你
Thank you so much.
有什么方法可以报答你吗
Is there any way we could pay you for your time?
不用不用  真的不必
No, no, absolutely not.
我很乐意帮忙
I'm happy to help.
让我帮忙你们重置胎压检测系统
But let me just reset your tire-pressure monitor
这样它才不会一直发出警示音
so that thing doesn't beep at you all day.
好的  去吧  劳烦你了
Yes, please. Go right ahead.
看到了吗  莉莉
See that, Lily?
我们不需要男人来解救我们
We didn't need a man to help us get out of this.
当女人对别的女人伸出援手时就是这样
This is what happens when women help other women.
她应该只是确定一下有没有修好吧
She's probably just making sure it works, right?
那个贱人偷走了我的车
So that bitch stole my car.
往好的方面看  看到一名女性打入
On a positive note, it is nice to see a woman
曾是男性主导的行业领域也很棒
break into a previously male-dominated field.
我的化妆品不在保险里
My makeup was not insured.
这是完美解决方法啊
It's the perfect solution.
我们不能就做个决定就行了吗
Can't we just make an decision?
怎么了
What's going on?
你爸跟我在争一件事
Oh, your father and I have been arguing about something
争了一个多小时了
for over an hour.
幸好  我做了个特别的硬币
Fortunately, I've made a special coin
一面是我的脸  一面是你妈的脸
with my face on one side and your mom's on the other.
像女权斗士纪念币的丑版
Ugh, Susan B. Unflattering.
好的  来吧
Okay, here we go.
-是克莱尔那面  -赞
- It came up Claire. - Yep!
以后火葬
Getting cremated!
靠
Damn it!
好的  还有一题
Okay, here's another one...
我那面  我们用储备金买海边公寓
my head, we use our nest egg for a beach condo.
你那面  就留给孩子当应急金
Yours, the kids' safety net.
干嘛这样
Hey, not cool.
抱歉啦  孩子们
I'm so sorry, you guys.
你们还是可以来探望我们啊
Aw, you can come visit.
前提是你们有钱来
You know, if you can afford it.